CV of Jonathan Pam

DOB: 02/02/1989 Age 30 1 Manston Crescent, Leeds, LS15 8QZ E-mail: jonny pam@hotmail.co.uk

Mobile: 07588 580 837

Personal Profile

I have been working in the electrotechnical field for over 10 years, during this time I have installed and serviced a wide range equipment in both domestic and commercial premises. I have learnt to become proactive and efficient whilst working in demanding field service roles and possess a can-do mentality to ensure all aspects of my job role are carried out in a timely manner. My roles have always been customer facing which have enabled me to obtain excellent communication skills. I also hold a full clean UK driving licence.

Employment

Steeper Group (Assistive Technology Division): June 2010 – Present

Employed as a Field Engineer, I manage a Yorkshire wide client base designing and installing electronic assistive technology systems to promote greater independence for the less abled. Such technology includes intercoms, motorised multipoint locks, telephony, automatic door operators, nurse-call systems and automated curtain/blind/window openers. These are interfaced with and programmed to a suited medical device which is then controlled by specialised switches or eye tracking devices. My responsibilities begin at the assessment stage right through to the ongoing maintenance. Other duties include electrical work and certification, quality assurance, training and R&D work.

Optica Security Systems: October 2006 - June 2010

I joined Optica as an apprentice where I attended college for 3 years. After qualifying I remained employed as an Electronics Engineer installing and servicing intruder alarms, CCTV, access control and public address systems, be it working alone in domestic properties or as part of a team on a large project.

Education

Trade Skills 4U City & Guilds Full Inspection and Testing 2391-52	Grade Booked	Year 2019
Scantime Training PLC Programming Series	Grade Currently st	Year udying
Open Study College Flectrical Theory and Maintenance NCFF Level 3	Grade Distinction	Year 2019

Trade Skills 4U City & Guilds Domestic Installation workshop 4141-01 City & Guilds Part P Building regulations 2393 City & Guilds Inspection and Testing 2392-10 City & Guilds 18 th Edition wiring regulations 2382	Grade Pass Pass Pass Pass	Year 2019 2019 2019 2019
Teeside University Foundation Mathematics for Engineering (COL0001N-WEB)	Grade Distinction	Year 2015
BTEC- Health care and Assistive Technology Level 4 To deliver an enhanced person-centred service to	Grade	Year
Reighley College - September 2006 to July 2009 City & Guilds Advanced Apprenticeship in Security Systems NVQ Level 3	Pass Grade	2015 Year
 Providing security, emergency & alarm systems Electrical Principles Minimise and respond to health and safety risks in your workplace. Communicate effectively in the workplace. Contribute to maintaining effective working relationships. Make preparations and arrangements to install security, emergency or alarm systems. Install cabling for security, emergency or alarm systems. Install security, emergency or alarm equipment. Test and confirm operation security, emergency or alarm systems. 	NVQ Level 2 Credit Credit Credit Credit Credit Credit Credit Credit Credit	2008
 Providing security, emergency & alarm systems Survey sites to prepare specifications of security, emergency or alarm systems. Plan the installation of security, emergency or alarm systems and services. Audit security, emergency or alarm systems. Commission and hand over security, emergency or alarm systems achieve objectives. Maintain the performance of security, emergency or alarm systems. Demonstrate the use of and hand over security, emergency or alarm systems to customers. Implement works to meet installation requirements. 	NVQ Level 3 Credit Credit Credit Credit Credit Credit Credit	2010

Roundhay Technology College / High School: September 2000 – July 2006

Qualification Grade Year

Mathematics	GCSE 'B'	2005
English	GCSE 'C'	2005
English Literature	GCSE 'C'	2005
French	GCSE 'C'	2005
Science	GCSE 'CC'	2005
Media Studies	GCSE 'C'	2005
Information & Communication Technology	OCR 'Level 2'	2005
Sociology	GCE AS 'C'	2006

Interests

I enjoy keeping fit by going to the gym and playing football. I am a Keen DIYer currently renovating my house.